[
  {
    "name": "Aj's Quiz on memes",
    "desc": "This is a quiz on memes pepelaugh",
    "quizBody": [
      { "question": "what is memes", "answer": "he is a green frog", "id": 0, "isHidden": false },
      { "question": "what is pepe 2", "answer": "he is a green frog 2", "id": 1, "isHidden": true },
      { "question": "what is pepe 3", "answer": "he is a green frog 3", "id": 2, "isHidden": true }
    ],
    "id": "71ebbb2a-97ba-4c5f-8855-1e18984d8828"
  },
  {
    "name": "Aj's Quiz on memes 2",
    "desc": "This is a quiz on memes pepelaugh 2",
    "quizBody": [
      { "question": "what is pepe", "answer": "he is a green frog", "id": 0, "isHidden": false },
      { "question": "what is pepe 2", "answer": "he is a green frog 2", "id": 1, "isHidden": true },
      { "question": "what is pepe 3", "answer": "he is a green frog 3", "id": 2, "isHidden": true }
    ],
    "id": "67df74e4-5617-45cc-ad94-c46186fff680"
  },
  {
    "name": "Frontend stuff",
    "desc": "This is a quiz on Frontend",
    "quizBody": [
      { "question": "q1", "answer": "he is a green frog", "id": 0, "isHidden": false },
      { "question": "q2", "answer": "he is a green frog 2", "id": 1, "isHidden": true },
      { "question": "q3", "answer": "he is a green frog 3", "id": 2, "isHidden": true }
    ],
    "id": "e74651ac-85ca-47da-947f-ccefac59d403"
  },
  {
    "name": "Ethan's Big Fat Quiz",
    "desc": "Its a Quiz, Its big and its fat",
    "quizBody": [
      { "question": "q1", "answer": "a1", "id": 0, "isHidden": false },
      { "question": "q2", "answer": "a2", "id": 1, "isHidden": true },
      { "question": "q3", "answer": "a3", "id": 2, "isHidden": true }
    ],
    "id": "ace271b9-8a84-4d89-a6b8-e3287e5f3c7f"
  }
]
